새벽 네 시 모니터 하나 켜놓고
At four AM, with one monitor on,
줄줄이 코드를 써 내려가
Writing line after line of code.
에러 백 개쯤 지우고 나면
After deleting about a hundred errors,
캐릭터 하나가 눈을 떠
One character opens its eyes.
아무도 모르는 이 작은 세계
This small world, unknown to anyone,
내 손끝에서 태어나는 중
Is being born from my fingertips.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating a dream within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up one space at a time.
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing over a bug-ridden night,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My own game begins.
완성 버튼을 누르는 그날
The day I press the 'complete' button,
온 세상이 플레이하게 될 거야
The whole world will get to play it.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating a dream within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up one space at a time.
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing over a bug-ridden night,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My own game begins.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating a dream within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up one space at a time,
이 밤의 코드가 빛이 돼
This night's code becomes light.